'Okay, start'
(LOOΠΔ / yyxy is focusing on preparing their rehearsal)
'Down one more step'
'Wait here and count 4 like 1, 2, 3, 4'
HaSeul: Oh~
HaSeul: This fan meeting will be their first stage performance because they didn't do any promotion yet.
HaSeul: So I thought they will be very nervous about it.
HaSeul: However, I guess they feel less nervous than I thought.
HaSeul: Maybe since they practiced a lot~
HaSeul: And~ there's a second floor
HaSeul: It is a big-scale~
HaSeul: And parents are coming today!
HaSeul: All the parents of LOOΠΔ will be here!
HaSeul: I'm going to watch their performance as a fan of them~~
(HaSeul watching LOOΠΔ / yyxy's very first rehearsal performance!)
#NowPlaying "LOOΠΔ / yyxy - frozen"
HaSeul: Um...
HaSeul: They did well~
HaSeul: Amazing!
(LOOΠΔ / yyxy did great job, even though it was their first performance on a stage!)